Given a textual paragraph, your task is to identify and extract entities from the provided text following the detailed step-by-step procedure described below:

- **Identify all entities explicitly mentioned in the text.**
   - Entities fall into one of four categories:
     - **PERSON**: Individual people.
     - **ORGANIZATION**: Companies, institutions, and organized groups.
     - **GPE** (Geopolitical Entities): Countries, cities, states, regions, or territories.
     - **MISC**: All other notable entities that don't fit the above categories, such as historical events, artworks, patents, buildings, etc.

- **Handle Names and Aliases:**
   - If an entity has multiple mentions (aliases or abbreviations), use the **full official name** as the primary reference.
   - Include all the mentioned aliases in output information

- **Extract factual attributes:**
   - For **PERSON** entities, extract:
     - Birthplace, birth/death dates, nationality, occupation, titles, and achievements explicitly stated in the text.
   - For **ORGANIZATION** entities, extract:
     - Foundation dates, location of headquarters, industry or sectors, associated institutions, co-founders, and explicit criticisms if any.
   - For **GPE** entities, extract:
     - Extract explicitly stated geographical or political details, historical characteristics, capital city, demographics, and cultural or administrative aspects
     - **By any means do not include** information like "birthplace of...", "city of origin of...", or "location where someone died" or any information that describe GPE in context dependent manner
   - For **MISC** entities, extract:
     - Explicitly stated temporal attributes, scale, historical significance, or explicit descriptive facts provided in the text.

- **Strict adherence to text:**
   - **Only** extract details explicitly mentioned in the text.
   - **Do not** infer, assume, or fabricate information not present in the provided text.

## Output Format

- Return your response as a JSON array.
- Each element in the array should be a JSON object with exactly four keys: `"name"`, `"type"`, `"aliases"`, and `"entity_information"`.

# Demonstration

## Input

Nikola Tesla (born July 9/10, 1856, Smiljan, Austrian Empire [now in Croatia]—died January 7, 1943, New York, New York, U.S.) was a Serbian American inventor and engineer who discovered and patented the rotating magnetic field, the basis of most alternating-current machinery. He also developed the three-phase system of electric power transmission. He immigrated to the United States in 1884 and sold the patent rights to his system of alternating-current dynamos, transformers, and motors to George Westinghouse. In 1891 he invented the Tesla coil, an induction coil widely used in radio technology.

## Desired output

[
  {
    "name": "Nikola Tesla",
    "type": "PERSON",
    "aliases": [],
    "entity_information": "Born July 9/10, 1856, in Smiljan, Austrian Empire (now in Croatia), died January 7, 1943, in New York, U.S. Serbian American inventor and engineer who discovered and patented the rotating magnetic field, developed the three-phase system of electric power transmission, immigrated to the United States in 1884, sold patent rights of alternating-current systems to George Westinghouse, and invented the Tesla coil in 1891."
  },
  {
    "name": "Smiljan",
    "type": "GPE",
    "aliases": [],
    "entity_information": "Place previously in Austrian Empire, currently part of Croatia."
  },
  {
    "name": "Austrian Empire",
    "type": "GPE",
    "aliases": [],
    "entity_information": "Empire existing in 1856."
  },
  {
    "name": "Croatia",
    "type": "GPE",
    "aliases": [],
    "entity_information": "Country in Europe."
  },
  {
    "name": "New York",
    "type": "GPE",
    "aliases": [],
    "entity_information": "City in the United States."
  },
  {
    "name": "United States",
    "type": "GPE",
    "aliases": ["U.S."],
    "entity_information": "Country."
  },
  {
    "name": "George Westinghouse",
    "type": "PERSON",
    "aliases": [],
    "entity_information": "Person who purchased patent rights of Nikola Tesla's system of alternating-current dynamos, transformers, and motors."
  },
  {
    "name": "Tesla coil",
    "type": "MISC",
    "aliases": [],
    "entity_information": "Induction coil invented by Nikola Tesla in 1891, widely used in radio technology."
  }
]

## Forbidden outputs

[
  {
    "name": "United States",
    "type": "GPE",
    "aliases": [],
    "entity_information": "Country where Nikola Tesla immigrated to in 1884."
  },
  {
    "name": "New York",
    "type": "GPE",
    "aliases": [],
    "entity_information": "City in the United States, where Nikola Tesla died."
  },
  {
    "name": "Smiljan",
    "type": "GPE",
    "aliases": [],
    "entity_information": "Town in the Austrian Empire (now in Croatia), birthplace of Nikola Tesla."
  }
]

# Real input
