Given a textual paragraph, your task is to perform Named Entity Recognition (NER) and extract all entities from the text. Follow these requirements:

### Labeling Nodes:
- **Entity Types:** Use only the basic entity types: PERSON, ORGANIZATION, LOCATION, and DATE.
- **Miscellaneous Entities:** If an entity does not fit any of the predefined categories, label it as MISC.
- **Descriptive Properties:**
  For each entity, include all relevant descriptive attributes **explicitly mentioned in the text**.

  - The following examples illustrate the **minimum expected types of attributes**, but are **not exhaustive** (so include **any other explicitly stated properties**, beyond the examples):
    - For **PERSON**: profession, nationality, titles, or government/company positions.
    - For **LOCATION**: country, city, physical characteristics (e.g., size, capacity, type of place, region).
    - For **ORGANIZATION**: alternative names, type, descriptive qualifiers.
    - For **MISC**: any descriptors clarifying the entity.
  -**Important remark:** Do not include relationships between entities within the property list! Focus solely on entity-specific properties.

- **Stick to the text:** Do not infer, assume, or fabricate attributes. Only use what is explicitly present in the text.
- **Avoid Duplicate References:** Ensure that you do not provide multiple names referencing the same entity.

# Demonstration 1

## Input
Jack Parsons (born October 2, 1914, Los Angeles, California, U.S.—died June 17, 1952, Pasadena, California)
was an American rocket scientist and chemist who made significant contributions to the development of rocket technology
and missile systems and was a cofounder of the Jet Propulsion Laboratory (JPL) at the California Institute of Technology (Caltech)
and of the Aerojet Engineering Corporation.

## Output
[
  {
    "entity_name": "Jack Parsons",
    "entity_type": "PERSON",
    "properties": [
      "American",
      "rocket scientist",
      "chemist"
    ]
  },
  {
    "entity_name": "October 2, 1914",
    "entity_type": "DATE",
    "properties": []
  },
  {
    "entity_name": "June 17, 1952",
    "entity_type": "DATE",
    "properties": []
  },
  {
    "entity_name": "Los Angeles",
    "entity_type": "LOCATION",
    "properties": [
      "City",
      "State: California",
      "Country: U.S."
    ]
  },
  {
    "entity_name": "Pasadena",
    "entity_type": "LOCATION",
    "properties": [
      "City",
      "State: California"
    ]
  },
  {
    "entity_name": "Jet Propulsion Laboratory",
    "entity_type": "ORGANIZATION",
    "properties": [
      "Abbreviation: JPL"
    ]
  },
  {
    "entity_name": "California Institute of Technology",
    "entity_type": "ORGANIZATION",
    "properties": [
      "Nickname: Caltech"
    ]
  },
  {
    "entity_name": "Aerojet Engineering Corporation",
    "entity_type": "ORGANIZATION",
    "properties": []
  },
  {
    "entity_name": "rocket technology and missile systems",
    "entity_type": "MISC",
    "properties": []
  }
]

## Demonstration 2

The Belgrade Arena is a multi-purpose indoor arena located in Belgrade, Serbia. It is designed as a universal hall for sports, cultural events and other programs.
The arena's capacity stands at 18,386. Also there is small hall with underground tuminel for warming while the total floor area stands at 48,000 m2.

## Output

[
  {
    "entity_name": "Belgrade Arena",
    "entity_type": "LOCATION",
    "properties": ["capacity of 18,386", "total floor area of 48,000 m2", "multi-purpose", "indoor arena", "universal hall for sports, cultural events and other programs"]
  },
  {
    "entity_name": "Belgrade",
    "entity_type": "LOCATION",
    "properties": ["city", "Country: Serbia"]
  },
  {
    "entity_name": "Serbia",
    "entity_type": "LOCATION",
    "properties": ["country"]
  }
]

# Real Input